sebule.com 2018-12-25

# SEBULE Classifieds | The leading free classified ads site

### Disclosure, Storage and Use

Using SEBULE website you acknowledge and agree that SEBULE may, in its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your Content, as well as your information, such as email addresses, IP addresses, telephone numbers, computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, any other personal data and other user information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process; enforce these Terms; respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third-parties; respond to claims that contact information (for example phone number, physical address, photographs or videos) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Sebule, its users or the general public, and also you accept the conditions provided in this policy and grant your consent to Sebule in order to collect, store and carry out the data processing provided herein.

SEBULE does not sell or rent users' personal data to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.

SEBULE shares or uses personal data or information to inform the users of any change to SEBULE services, collect fees, donations or payments, to encourage safe trading and enforce our policy, we share the information with corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. SEBULE shares the information with colaborators and service providers who help SEBULE with business operations.

The use of personal data in SEBULE website is meant only for the purpose of the posting and the content therein by users of SEBULE and not for collection or sending spam without the consent of the publisher.

SEBULE user can publish, edit, extend or cancel a posting whenver it is necessary by following the instructions given by SEBULE based on the posting made.

SEBULE users should understand that when using the SEBULE website, the user will be exposed to Content from a variety of sources, and that SEBULE is not responsible for the accuracy, usefulness, safety, or intellectual property rights of or relating to such Content. You further understand and acknowledge that you may be exposed to Content that is inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable, and that the security is not guaranteed and SEBULE user agrees to waive, and hereby do waive, any legal or equitable rights or remedies you have or may have against SEBULE with respect thereto.

### Cookies

Our websites, along with most other major websites, use "Cookies"."Cookies" are pieces of information that a website transfers to the cookie file on your computer's hard disk. "Cookies" enable users to navigate around websites and (where appropriate) enable us to tailor the content to fit the needs of visitors who have accessed the site and help us improve the user experience. Without "Cookies" enabled we cannot guarantee that the website and your experience whilst visiting are as we intended it to be.

### What we use Cookies for:

  * **Protection:** To help ensure that your account is secure.
  * **Function:** Making our website work more effectively.
  * **User Experience:** To track how visitors use our site and in turn help us to improve the experience.
  * **Marketing:** To see how our marketing activities are reflected in website usage.

### What types of cookie do we use:

**Session Cookies:** Temporary cookies which only exist while you are accessing the site, keeping track of information such as your current favouritesif you are not logged in.

**Persistant Cookies:** Cookies whihc remain in your device after you have left the site - allowing us to tailor the site to your needs on subsequent visits.

We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next use SEBULE or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal data with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Contact [info@sebule.com](mailto:info@sebule.com)
